A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer), Series 23 FA366
Rockefeller Archive Center
Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Civil Service Resolutions (Charles H. Palmer), Series 23
1959-1973
Rockefeller Archive Center
New York (State). State Commission for Human Rights
Whitman, Ann
Cannon, James M.
New York (State). Dept. of Civil Service
Boyd, Joseph H.
Ronan, William J. (William John)
Morrow, Hugh
New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller)
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA366
4 record cartons
Biographical/Historical note
Nelson A. Rockefeller served as governor of New York from January 1, 1959, to December 18, 1973. He was the first person elected to four consecutive four-year terms as a state governor.
File Plan note
Former Classification: III 15 23
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for scholarly research, except where particular restrictions are noted.
RAC is unable to provide access to obsolete media and original digital media. In addition separated media may not yet have undergone stabilization procedures. When feasible, a digital surrogate may be created via special order. All applicable charges will apply. See RAC Head of Archival Services or RAC Head of Digital Programs for details.
Scope and Contents note
This series is a collection of resolutions forwarded to Charles H. Palmer, Assistant Secretary to the Governor for Reports, from the New York Department of Civil Service. Each year of Governor Rockefeller's gubernatorial tenure is represented by resolutions that were approved by Governor Rockefeller on Palmer's recommendation and those resolutions that were "Withdrawn or Withheld" at the request of the Civil Service Department head. Resolutions would be withdrawn or withheld as a result of the information being superceded by a subsequent resolution or the reasons for the resolution being resolved in some other manner.
Civil Service Resolutions were adopted by New York State to increase or decrease the number of positions in the state government. Resolutions were not specific to an individual, but rather to a position or title.
Other Finding Aids note
Detailed finding aids for each series of this collection are available:
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Appointments Office (FA353)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Assembly and Senate Memos (FA354)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Joseph H. Boyd (FA355)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, James Cannon (FA356)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Affirmative Action (N. Lee Cook) (FA357)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Counsel's Office (FA358)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York State Committee to Reelect the President (FA359)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Jerry A. Danzig (FA360)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Executive Chamber (FA361)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, 55th Street (FA362)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Issue Books (FA363)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Arthur Massolo (FA364)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Hugh Morrow (FA242)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Office (FA365)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Political Files (FA367)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Press Office (FA368)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Public Relations (FA369)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Departmental Reports (FA370)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, William J. Ronan (FA371)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Speeches (FA372)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Diane Van Wie (FA373)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Ann C. Whitman, Gubernatorial (FA374)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, Gene Wyckoff (FA375)
Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial Records, New York Republican State Fund Raising Reports (FA376)
Civil defense -- United States; Civil service; Arms control -- United States; Civil defense; Federal government -- United States; Government policy; Civil service -- New York (State); Economics; International relations; International economic relations; Latin America; International relations -- United States; Affirmative action programs -- New York (State); Arms control; Human rights; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1970; Political science; Presidential campaigns -- United States; Legislation -- New York (State); New York (N.Y.); New York (State); Political campaigns -- United States; Vice-Presidents -- United States; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1962; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1958; Presidential candidates -- United States -- History -- 20th century; Governors -- Election -- New York (State) -- 1966; Public relations; Public policy; United States; State governments -- United States; New York (State). State Commission for Human Rights; Whitman, Ann; Republican Party (U.S.: 1854- ); Cannon, James M.; New York (State). Dept. of Civil Service; Boyd, Joseph H.; Ronan, William J. (William John); Morrow, Hugh; New York (State). Governor (1959-1973: Rockefeller); Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
- Approval Completed, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Correspondence, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Approval Completed, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Approval Completed, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Approval Completed, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Approval Completed, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Approval Completed, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Approval Completed, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Approval Completed, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Approval Completed, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Approval Completed, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Approval Completed, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Approval Completed, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Approval Completed, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Approval Completed, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Approval Completed, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Approval Completed, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Approval Completed, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Approval Completed, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Approval Completed, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Approval Completed, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Approval Completed, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Approval Completed, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Approval Completed, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Approval Completed, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Approval Completed, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Approval Completed, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Approval Completed, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Approval Completed, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Approval Completed, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Approval Completed, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
- Approval Completed, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
- Approval Completed, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 42)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 43)
- Approval Completed, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 44)
- Approval Completed, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 45)
- Approval Completed, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 46)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 47)
- Approval Completed, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Approval Completed, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 49)
- Approval Completed, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 50)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 51)
- Approval Completed, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 52)
- Approval Completed, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 53)
- Approval Completed, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 54)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 55)
- Approval Completed, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 56)
- Approval Completed, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 57)
- Approval Completed, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Approval Completed, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 59)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 60)
- Approval Completed, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 61)
- Approval Completed, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 62)
- Approval Completed, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 63)
- Approval Completed, 1973 (Box 4, Folder 64)
- Withdrawn or Withheld, 1974 (Box 4, Folder 65)